<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Daventry Vaulters League feed</title>
    <link>http://www.level10.org/BloodBowl</link>
    <description>Blood bowl league RSS feed</description>
    <language>en-EN</language>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 16:39:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>OBBLM 0.96</generator>
    <item>
      <title>Match: Ziggy's Spiders (1) vs. Horns &amp; Spikes (2)</title>
      <description>Tight first half ended 1-1 and with little blood, but crucially Ziggy the str4 catcher stayed in the KO box.&#xD;
Receiving in the second half the chaos grind made slow progress until halfway through the half, chaos dice ran hot and put half the elf team in the injury box, nothing serious but left the elf&#x2019;s watching on as the turn 8 score secured the 2-1 win.</description>
      <link>http://www.level10.org/BloodBowl</link>
      <pubDate>2017-11-09 18:26:08</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match: Masons Guild (0) vs. Tomb Raiders (1)</title>
      <description>Despite hoards of guard and grinding the undead into the dirt there was a single casualty in the whole match as the KO boxes saw plenty of use.</description>
      <link>http://www.level10.org/BloodBowl</link>
      <pubDate>2017-11-09 13:00:33</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match: Weborn Wodents (0) vs. Dockside Brawlers (1)</title>
      <description>Brutal ! Once the Brawlers had players up, it was a blood bath! </description>
      <link>http://www.level10.org/BloodBowl</link>
      <pubDate>2017-11-09 08:40:34</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match: Eshinobi Rising (2) vs. Cleaverland Browns (3)</title>
      <description>Congrats to Drazgon for his first competitive 1TTD.</description>
      <link>http://www.level10.org/BloodBowl</link>
      <pubDate>2017-11-08 23:50:27</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match: Dav City All Starz (1) vs. Hamma' &amp; Tongs (1)</title>
      <description>match unplayed..</description>
      <link>http://www.level10.org/BloodBowl</link>
      <pubDate>2017-11-06 12:59:58</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match: Ziggy's Spiders (1) vs. Neues Emskrank Corsairs (1)</title>
      <description>A game of the mundane and the insane.  A dropped regulation catch to go 1-0 up early left the elves on scramble defence all half - first sacking the quarterback only for the dump-off to deny them, and then triple coverage not proving enough for the blitzer who dodged to the end zone to await Griff's pass: 1-0.  The second half the humans went tortoise, but were finally worn down and this time the dump off was intercepted and the elves won the foot race for honours to be tied at the final whistle.</description>
      <link>http://www.level10.org/BloodBowl</link>
      <pubDate>2017-11-04 10:07:37</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match: Cleaverland Browns (3) vs. Dav City All Starz (2)</title>
      <description>The difference between the 2 teams was a timely perfect defence vs no reroll frogs gifting a turnover</description>
      <link>http://www.level10.org/BloodBowl</link>
      <pubDate>2017-11-03 23:22:19</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match: Weborn Wodents (2) vs. Masons Guild (1)</title>
      <description>Aside from the freshly-returned Rogre crippling himself before the starting whistle finished echoing about the Wodent's rickety stands, there was practically no bloodshed or casualty carnage. not for lack of trying. Heck, the Mason's even managed to bring their deathroller onto the field for three drives during the entire second half thanks to shoddy skaven stadium maintenance. :O It didn't help. In fact, this probably was the cause of a disgruntled fan KOing skaven blitzer Pyko with a well-aimed commemorative Bugman's stein during the set up for the final drive. Dwarf brew certainly went straight to his head :).&#xD;
&#xD;
Anyhow, the ratties actually managed to scrape a 2-1 win, but this was entirely down to some gentlemanly blitzing from the Mason's runner, Vysh Ironbeard, who gave gutter runner, shuffti "Shenanigens" Malarkee a enthusiastic shove towards his end zone rather than bodyslam the little rat into the turf. Was he drunk, concussed, or maybe even struck down with remorse at the pitiful whiskered ratty face imploring him earnestly? We don't know exactly, but there's sure to be an investigation for this incredulous example of "fair play" and sportsmanship.&#xD;
&#xD;
</description>
      <link>http://www.level10.org/BloodBowl</link>
      <pubDate>2017-11-03 23:04:14</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match: Eshinobi Rising (0) vs. Tomb Raiders (1)</title>
      <description>The rats join an exclusive club of teams that haven't thrashed the undead this season.</description>
      <link>http://www.level10.org/BloodBowl</link>
      <pubDate>2017-11-01 23:30:40</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match: Dockside Brawlers (1) vs. Chaos Khorne and Bred (0)</title>
      <description>Match unplayed</description>
      <link>http://www.level10.org/BloodBowl</link>
      <pubDate>2017-10-31 13:42:25</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match: Horns &amp; Spikes (1) vs. Hamma' &amp; Tongs (0)</title>
      <description>Not the blood bath predicted, crowd trouble at the start of the game put half the players on the ground which really stalled the dwarf drive and allowed the H&amp;S the hold the first half scoreless &#xD;
The normally deadly dwarfs couldn&#x2019;t gain their usual player advantage and couldn&#x2019;t hold off the turn 8 score, for a grindy 1-0 win to the chaos</description>
      <link>http://www.level10.org/BloodBowl</link>
      <pubDate>2017-10-26 21:27:45</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match: Dockside Brawlers (1) vs. Masons Guild (0)</title>
      <description>Dwarf cages are tough.............!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! And Deathrollers are just wrong :-)</description>
      <link>http://www.level10.org/BloodBowl</link>
      <pubDate>2017-10-20 08:29:25</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match: Horns &amp; Spikes (1) vs. Weborn Wodents (0)</title>
      <description>Rats seemed to have the upper hand right from turn 1 blitz and only white line fever prevented a rat score&#xD;
Impotent chaos lucky to scrape a win and stay in the title hunt</description>
      <link>http://www.level10.org/BloodBowl</link>
      <pubDate>2017-10-19 19:07:31</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match: Chaos Khorne and Bred (0) vs. Dav City All Starz (1)</title>
      <description>match unplayed</description>
      <link>http://www.level10.org/BloodBowl</link>
      <pubDate>2017-10-19 06:33:27</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match: Tomb Raiders (2) vs. Neues Emskrank Corsairs (1)</title>
      <description>Could've gone either way, both sides had long passes to win, difference turned out to be a skeleton interception.</description>
      <link>http://www.level10.org/BloodBowl</link>
      <pubDate>2017-10-18 22:28:00</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match: Eshinobi Rising (0) vs. Hamma' &amp; Tongs (2)</title>
      <description>One badly rolled gfi allowed the dwarves to dominate and get payback for street bowl.</description>
      <link>http://www.level10.org/BloodBowl</link>
      <pubDate>2017-10-18 21:26:25</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match: Cleaverland Browns (0) vs. Ziggy's Spiders (2)</title>
      <description>In the race for best ineptitude the humans managed to just pip the elves to the post as for all their floundering and tripping themselves up the elves managed 1 turn of beauty to secure the game at the final stages.</description>
      <link>http://www.level10.org/BloodBowl</link>
      <pubDate>2017-10-11 22:43:56</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match: Dav City All Starz (0) vs. Horns &amp; Spikes (2)</title>
      <description>Match started with a blitz handing the ball to the chaos, and it was downhill all the way for the frogs from there, as they hugged the side lines and ran away.&#xD;
&#xD;
Fresh from the Frog coach: "Fouls hurt!!"</description>
      <link>http://www.level10.org/BloodBowl</link>
      <pubDate>2017-10-06 19:52:14</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match: Neues Emskrank Corsairs (2) vs. Cleaverland Browns (3)</title>
      <description>Zug issued the beatings along with Josie as the Corsair numbers dwindled, they still managed to cling onto a draw until the last turn when the Browns Blitzers combined into a game winning play.</description>
      <link>http://www.level10.org/BloodBowl</link>
      <pubDate>2017-10-04 22:26:54</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Match: Hamma' &amp; Tongs (2) vs. Dockside Brawlers (1)</title>
      <description>The lack of skills and a poor rolls combined to make the game very painful for the necro's.</description>
      <link>http://www.level10.org/BloodBowl</link>
      <pubDate>2017-10-04 22:07:59</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
